Look, a win is a win for Manchester City
today, but I think this is one of those
wins that massively covers up the cracks
in this team. This is one of those wins
that you take the three points, but you
look at and say that was shocking. That
second half from Medster City is up
there with one of the worst performances
from a pep side I have seen in a half.
Honestly, I know last season they went
on that terrible losing run. I know in
the past as well too, they have
struggled. They haven't always been
perfect, but that's up there with or
rather down there with the worst I have
seen from a Guardiola team play.
Guardiola mentioned during the week
about wanting to see bravery from his
team. That loss against Leverkus and for
him even more damning than one against
Newcastle because he felt his side
didn't take enough risk. They didn't
show enough bravery on the ball to get
on it and make things happen and take
the game to the opposition. On the basis
of the first half, you would have
thought that his team definitely took
those words on board because they were
comfortable. Within a minute, Phil Foden
scoring a goal very similar to the one
he actually missed against Newcastle,
but this time getting good contact on it
to put his side up 1 nil after 40
seconds. And then shortly after,
Guardiola off a set piece bundling the
ball over the line after a bit of a
mishap from Leeds. And this game could
have very well been three or four nil
after the first half for Man City. As
you would typically expect, right? When
you see Man City playing at at home to
Leads, you expect that is a
straightforward, easy, take the three
points and just go home before ball is
even kicked. But then in the second
half, the ugly side of this City team
reared its ugly head. And it happened
very, very quickly. 5 minutes into the
second half. One of the worst defensive
mistakes you will see from a top side
this season in any league across Europe.
Guardial Nunes Nunez. Honestly, it's
just an absolute calamity from
Manchester City's defenders in a
situation where they really weren't in
any danger until they actually put
themselves in the danger. And Nunz in
particular, I don't think covers himself
in any kind of glory in this in this
moment. And to be honest with you, I
thought throughout the game, showed
tremendous weakness out there and maybe
reaffirms the belief that Manchester
City do need a right back going forward.
I know he's actually had a pretty decent
season over the course of this year, but
I think if City are serious about
challenging in every single competition,
like they typically do, Nunez is not the
level for Manchester City right back.
Not in my opinion. Cal Lewen capitalizes
on the mistake 2-1 to Manchester City.
But these are moments where in the past
few seasons you would see Man City
concede a goal. But rather than just
panic and lose their minds, no, what Man
City would do is get on the ball, put
their foot on it, slow the game down to
their tempo, and dictate the way the
rest of the game went because they
weren't afraid of conceding more. They
weren't afraid of what the opposition
could do to them because they knew the
quality that they had that could punish
them. That was the old Manchester City
where the likes of De Bruyne and Silva
and Fernandinho and Rodri when he was
fit. That's the Man City that went on to
win 12, 13 games in a row on course to
winning a Premier League title. But the
problem with this Man City team is at
the slightest sign of adversity, you do
feel like they are susceptible to
crumbling. I question the mentality of
this team. I don't really question the
talent of this team, but I do question
the mentality of this side. Do they
actually believe that they're good
enough to win a Premier League title?
Because on the basis of that second
half, I have to question that from a lot
of them. And the second goal that they
concede, Guardio sliding in the way he
did. Vardio scored a goal, was playing
decent, and then commits these stupid
mistakes that you just think to
yourself, Vardio, you're way better than
that. You're way better than that. It's
such a boneheaded tackle going directly
through Calvert Leuen. It's a stone cold
stonewall penalty. Obviously, Meta takes
the penalty. Donnaruma makes a really
good save and then the follow-up is
easy. It's a tap in 22. And on top of
that, it wasn't it's not bad enough that
they gave up a twogoal lead to make it
2-2. Even at 2-2 leads looked like the
side for a bit that were pushing for a
winner. They were the side that actually
had more possession after 60 minutes in
that second half than Man City at the
Etihad. This is for me shocking. It's
absolutely shocking to see a lead side
who have been so distinctly average
throughout this year playing away at one
of the toughest grounds supposedly to go
to in the Prem and actually taking the
game to Man City even at 22. And
genuinely I think City are very very
fortunate with how the second half went
in that they never conceded the third
because at times it was disgraceful for
a side with title aspirations like we've
labeled the City team. Some of the play
in that second half was as poor as you
can get. Now where it all started to go
left for for leads was towards the last
5 to 10 minutes of the game and then of
course in extra time leads started to
retreat a little bit. Leads started to
secede possession a little bit. they
started to drop deeper and Manchester
City start to get a foothold in the
game. And we know the minute you start
allowing Man City to get a hold of the
ball and then dictating the way they
want to play, it's only a matter of
time. And then when you saw 10 minutes
added on on the board, come on. It it
almost felt like City were going to grab
grab a goal. But the goal that Phil
Fodden scores today is sensational.
That's a fantastic goal. And the timing
of it as well too is is ridiculous. But
Cherokee looks up, sees Foden in in a
good amount of space. Fodin receives the
ball almost on the H like across his
body. Allah Foden, we know that's his
specialty, right? But Leed's players
quickly close in on him. So the angle to
shoot is almost immediately destructed,
right? But Phil Foden shows all his
brilliant quality in this move. I think
first and foremost, like I said, to
receive it across his body, take that
touch and then have the footwork, have
the agility as well too to maneuver his
his way, maneuver the space to even
craft what in my opinion is a half
chance. that finish that he pulls off is
a half chance, man. He's not even fully
facing the goal. He's got bodies in
front of him. He's damn near on the edge
of the box and then to find an opening
the way he does with that finish.
Nothing Lucas Perry in the goal can do.
I think that's one of the best goals of
the season personally. And this is why I
continue to say Phil Foden. There's
numerous angles you can maybe look at
and criticize him for. I don't think
he's had a a perfect career today, but
one thing I can never ever ever doubt is
Phil Foden's talent. And in that moment
right there, it was on full display.
That is a fantastic goal, a fantastic
moment of individual brilliance to not
only get his team a win, but to save
their blushes and maybe save any little
title aspirations they do have because
at the moment, every game for City feels
like a must-win. When you look at the
form Arsenal are in at the moment in all
competitions, you look at the the mood
around that camp, you look at the
inevitability that they seem to be
displaying on a game-to-ame basis. As
Manchester City, you cannot afford to
slip up at any point, let alone playing
at home to leads. That has to be a
gimme. That has to be three easy points.
Game over before it even starts. They
made a very, very light situation
extremely difficult today. And they have
they have to anybody affiliated with
City today has to go and buy Phil Foden
dinner tonight because he's saved you
guys. But again, I don't think this is a
case of quality because you look at the
quality of Manchester City's players and
you look at the quality of leads and
it's night and day, right? No one would
dare say leads have as good players as
City. No one would dare say Daniel Farca
is on the same caliber of manager as Pep
Guardiola, but I'm telling you, I think
with City right now, it's a mentality
thing. I know I'm not saying they're as
good as Arsenal, right? But for me, the
the results over the last three weeks,
rather the performances over the last
three weeks, maybe especially the two
because I think Newcastle, they did
contest, they did have a few chances,
they could have easily won that game,
right? But the last two games, I'm just
looking at City at times and I'm like, I
don't know if they in their heart of
hearts believe that they have what it
takes to win the league. And it's kind
of why at the start of the season I said
I think City potentially have the
highest ceiling of any team if they can
kind of get everything clicking. But
also it's why I believe they're maybe a
year away from actually being a serious
Premier League contender. They're going
to contend, right? But can they go all
the way? I think they're a year away
from that. And it's not because I feel
like they have to buy six new players. I
feel like it's just they don't have
enough players that are ready for prime
time. They don't have enough players
that have been through numerous title
races. They have some obviously some
guys have won Premier Leagues for them,
but I think the players that they're
trying to incorporate into this team to
almost bow out the old guard, I don't
think they're ready yet to be going on,
like I said, 12, 13 game winning runs
like City usually do to then win the
Premier League at the end of the season.
I'm going to be honest, Tajani Rinders,
who looked so fantastic against Wolves
on opening day, has looked pretty
unremarkable since, and this is a player
I do rate, but I think he has massively
struggled to kind of get a run of games,
get a run of performances together. uh
and in fact he's pretty much lost his
spot over the last few weeks as City
have decided to go Niko Gonzalez and
Bernardo as a as a deeper two rather
than Riners and he got his opportunity
today from the start against leads and I
don't think he took it well enough
whatsoever. I think Bernardo Silva had a
poor game in my opinion and I think by
the way his dive I think he's extremely
fortunate not to get a second yellow. I
think if he's not on a yellow already
they're giving him a yellow. That's a
terrible dive and they had V on top of
that to look at it. I think he caught
life today. Erling Howland tried and he
tried. He didn't have his best game at
all, but this is I I know we talked
about last week, can City win when he
doesn't score. They got it done today,
but I think still there is that question
mark about who can cons consistently
step up if Halen isn't scoring goals.
Foden did a fantastic job of that today,
but they still do need more. I thought
Douku had a pretty unremarkable game as
well too. I think leadeds his right back
did a pretty decent job of him despite
him still having that cross that Marmush
should have scored at the end. But for
me, the story for City today is the
defense. All four of those guys, Nunz,
O'Reilly, Vardial, and Diaz from a
defensive point of view, not from a
going forward, not from creating
chances, not from scoring goals, from
just old-fashioned defending point of
view today is unacceptable. And I think
they have to look at Donnaruma a little
bit because I think he saved them a on a
few occasions. And I think Donnaruma was
extremely unlucky to concede two goals
today. And I think they have to to owe a
big apology to their forwards as well,
too. That back four nearly cost
Manchester City three points today.
Guardiola, if we know him well enough,
and we do, he's a fierce competitor, but
he's also a perfectionist. He will not
be happy with that three points today. I
know on on face value, they got the win.
But I'm telling you, Guardiola in the
dressing room after that game is letting
his team have it because in the position
of complete control that they were in
before a ball was kicked or before a
second half was kicked to that second
half, my goodness, I I struggle to see
what went wrong, what was said at
halftime, what happened to the
mentality? Horrible. And now all eyes
look forward to tomorrow. And again,
this is why this folding goal is so huge
because I think if Man City draw this
game, forget about even lose it, but if
they draw this game, we're an Arsenal
win tomorrow away at Stanford Bridge
from saying the title is over, right?
I'm not a fan of City. I'm not a fan of
Arsenal. I'm not a fan of Chelsea. Not a
fan of Liverpool, but I'm a fan of
competition. It's why last season I was
so frustrated with Arsenal because I
want to see Premier League title races
that are contested by at least two
teams, let alone three or four. I want
to see what we're calling the best
league in the world. I want to see that
at the top level. And I think last
season we had no title race whatsoever.
Liverpool in my opinion had that one by
January, February time. This season
Arsenal are brilliant and they deserve
to win it if they do, but I still want
to see a side go toe-to-toe with them or
at least keep the distance, keep pace
with them, keep keep them honest. You
know what I mean? I don't want to see
Arsenal after 20 games, they're all but
mathematically winners. Now they're
putting out second teams. I don't want
to see that. I want to see a team really
give them a go, if not two, if not
three. So for Manchester City, I don't
have any dog in this fight here, right?
I don't have any horse in this race, but
I do want to see other teams give
Arsenal a go this year. At the moment,
City probably look like the most likely
we're going to see Chelsea tomorrow as
well, too, cuz they've quietly kind of
got under the radar and find themselves
in second ahead of tomorrow's game. But
the question is, can Arsenal continue
their winning run or their unbeaten run
rather? It is a winning run at this
point. I think the last lost, not to be
fair, they dropped points to Sunderland.
or can Chelsea's big game heroics
continue and can Moresca get another big
result this time against Mikuel Arteta?
All to play for. Can't wait for
tomorrow's game. I'm also watching PSG
Monaco at at the moment as well too. So,
we'll have a review for that tomorrow in
our European segment. But Man City, you
guys caught life, man. Don't Wow, that
was risky, man. That That was close.
I'll see you guys soon. Peace.