I'm pretty sure you guys have seen the news say they
don't arrest this guy, Gentle De Yahoo, but there's a problem and
the problem lies in this video.
And if Hope Uzodinma is denying that he did not have any meeting
with Janto and, with my master and not the rest of the
commanders, if Hope Uzodinma swell over this, Hope Uzodinma must die.
And I am standing, making the world and our people
to understand the kind of evil man that Hope Uzodinma is.
Standing familiar, standing gidibam, gidibam, telling our people this.
If Hope Uzodinma did not have meeting with me and my master,
with other commanders, let I not be a… Now, after watching
this video, my question is this.
Did the Nigerian Army army arrest Gentle De Yahoo because of all the
atrocities he committed or because he did not start to call names?
Do you understand?
Because as short as this video, this video carries a lot of weight.
Carries a lot of weight.
This guy, they allege, said go get meeting with the present governor
of Imo State, Hope Uzodinma Uzodima. Do you understand?
And they even went further to say, Hope Uzodinma
should come out and swear. Now, I'm curious about the kind
is having with these guys.
These guys that are being linked with kidnapping and buying of people.
He even went further to say, Hope Uzodinma, the meeting with him and
other commanders with the master.
Boom!
Now they don't arrest the guy.
It's suspicious, It's suspicious.
Now, what if you say, let's say these guys start to talk
because they don't betray her.
Maybe one agreement is not going the way it's supposed to be.
But they say they don't arrest them.
But again, another thing is this.
Was there really terrorism?
Most of these guys, nah sponsor, did they sponsor them?
I don't watch, you see this Gentle De Yahoo?
Are they watching videos?
Steady.
You gon' know say this guy, nah sponsor, they sponsor him.
There's nothing it.
You gon' know say they sponsor the guy.
Do you understand?
You won't know.
It's clear.
It's clear on all his videos.
Go and watch them.
Do you understand?
It's clear.
Now make it make sense.
How did this guy get this kind of gun?
For his sidebush?
How? Shit, did he plug gun for three?
They block bullets for three.
There are a lot of questions that when you answer, when you
ask, if you connect all the dots, you will understand that a lot
of these things are not real.
What people don't understand is that just the way, if they ask you,
what do you do for a living,
You say, I am a banker.
I am an entrepreneur.
That's how some people's business is Nigerian Army.
What do you do for a living?
Nigerian Army is what they do for a living.
To cause problem and to make sure Nigerian Army does not work.
And that's how they make their own money and benefit from it.
And I'm talking about politics, politicians.
Do you understand?
Now let's go back again, where this guy get all these guns from?
All these gun guns, na army if you bring them come this country.
Na army if you bring all these guns come this country, or police.
Na military in general.
how did it get to his hand?
That's another thing. This guy don't commit.
Now, there's a particular video where he go viral at that time.
Where he said three guys, they for ground.
Him blast them, Yoshi shoot them.
No tool, no wear cloth for ground.
And no one just played the video because of community guidelines.
Now, in that video, he face no show.
The guy face no show, but if you hear the voice, the
voice did similar.
this guy don't commit one or two things since.
When I don't link him to insurgency, kidnapping
and all but I don't go carry on.
He start to call names now and they go carry on.
That's number one.
Number two, obviously I'll give him a peace deal as
Because even I think if that guy forecasting a peace deal,
there's nothing people cannot do again in this country.
You are giving a man that has been linked to quite a lot of civilians
in Nigerian Army, a lot of citizens.
Nigerian Army. Both women and children.
That's where they link to kidnappings.
That's where we say in all of these, a lot of lives of
our own Nigerian Army army, our own military men go down.
They give her a big steal and they watch the video.
I just they shake my head.
That's why you pack cartridge pack bullets full body They
talk and they watch them.
I just they shake and they laugh.
I say no if you look at it critically you will understand
That when they tell you that there's insurgency in Nigerian Army.
Yes We have to quote it that one wants to make our video Do you
understand or want to talk against it or want to talk about it?
But do these things really exist?
Do you understand?
They say, they go arrest one kidnapper.
They go arrest one, Boko Haram member.
Who brought them in before?
Who bring Boko Haram before?
Who bring them in?
The only time where all these politicians want me to pipe by
those boys, now when those boys don't rebel against them, when
the boys don't get carried away, the tools where they bring,
where they will take use of them to do politics for them.
The boys don't start to use them for their own thing.
At that time, the government didn't do anything.
But anyways, we are not going to talk about that.
My own bise, the question is this.
She will not arrest Gentle De Yahoo because he don't
commit a lot of atrocities.
We are going to link his name too.
Or because he don't start to call names when he
is not supposed to call.
You know, that's just my harmless question.
Or is it that he is lying against the governor?
is it possible that the governor did not have any meeting with him
or he's just lying or he's just saying it i want to know i'm
really curious what meeting is he talking about what was discussed
in this meeting you know it is to ask bro this country anyways