Okay,  so  I'm  pretty  sure  you
guys  have  seen  the  news  say  they
don't  arrest  this  guy,  General
Diyahu,  but  there's  a  problem  and
the  problem  lies  in  this  video.
And  if  Opus  Odima  is  denying
that  he  did  not  have  any  meeting
with  Janto  and,  uh,  with  my
master  and  not  the  rest  of  the
commanders,  if  Opus  Odima  swell
over  this,  Opus  Odima  must  die.
And  I  am  standing,  making
the  world  and  our  people
to  understand  the  kind  of
evil  man  that  Opus  Odima  is.
Standing  familiar,  standing  gidibam,
gidibam,  telling  our  people  this.
If  Opus  Odima  did  not  have
meeting  with  me  and  my  master,
with  other  commanders,  let  I
not  be  a...  Now,  after  watching
this  video,  my  question  is  this.
Did  the  Nigerian  army  arrest
General  Diyahu  because  of  all  the
atrocities  he  committed  or  because
he  did  not  start  to  call  names?
Do  you  understand?
Because  as  short  as  this  video,
this  video  carries  a  lot  of  weight.
Carries  a  lot  of  weight.
This  guy,  they  allege,  said  go  get
meeting  with  the  present  governor
of  Imo  State,  Hope  Odidika  Uzodima.
Do  you  understand?
And  they  even  went  further
to  say,  Hope  Uzodima
should  come  out  and  swear.
Now,  I'm  curious  about  the  kind
of  meeting  that  the  governor
is  having  with  these  guys.
These  guys  that  are  being  linked
with  kidnapping  and  buying  of  people.
He  even  went  further  to  say,  Opozo
Nima,  the  meeting  with  him  and
other  commanders  with  the  master.
Boom!
Now  they  don't  arrest  the  guy.
It's  suspicious,  right?
It's  suspicious.
Now,  what  if  you  say,  let's
say  these  guys  start  to  talk
because  they  don't  betray  her.
Maybe  one  agreement  is  not  going
the  way  it's  supposed  to  be.
But  yeah,  they  say
they  don't  arrest  them.
But  again,  another  thing  is  this.
Was  there  really  terrorism?
Most  of  these  guys,  nah
sponsor,  did  they  sponsor  them?
I  don't  watch,  you  see
this  general  at  Yahoo?
Are  they  watching  videos?
Steady.
You  gon'  know  say  this  guy,
nah  sponsor,  they  sponsor  him.
There's  nothing  like  it.
You  gon'  know  say
they  sponsor  the  guy.
Do  you  understand?
You  won't  know.
It's  clear.
It's  clear  on  all  his  videos.
Go  and  watch  them.
Do  you  understand?
It's  clear.
Now  make  it  make  sense.
How  did  this  guy  get
this  kind  of  gun?
For  his  sidebush?
How?
Shit,  did  he  plug  gun  for  three?
They  block  bullets  for  three.
There  are  a  lot  of  questions
that  when  you  answer,  when  you
ask,  if  you  connect  all  the  dots,
you  will  understand  that  a  lot
of  these  things  are  not  real.
What  people  don't  understand  is  that
just  the  way,  if  they  ask  you,
what  do  you  do  for  a  living,  right?
You  say,  oh,  I  am  a  banker.
I  am  an  entrepreneur.
That's  how  some  people's
business  is  Nigeria.
What  do  you  do  for  a  living?
Nigeria  is  what  they
do  for  a  living.
To  cause  problem  and  to  make
sure  Nigeria  does  not  work.
And  that's  how  they  make  their
own  money  and  benefit  from  it.
And  I'm  talking  about
politics,  politicians.
Do  you  understand?
Now  let's  go  back  again,  where
this  guy  get  all  these  guns  from?
All  these  gun  guns,  na  army  if
you  bring  them  come  this  country.
Na  army  if  you  bring  all  these
guns  come  this  country,  or  police.
Na  military  in  general.
So  how  did  it  get  to  his  hand?
That's  another  thing.
This  guy  don't  commit.
Now,  there's  a  particular  video
where  he  go  viral  at  that  time.
Where  he  said  three
guys,  they  for  ground.
Him  blast  them,  Yoshi  shoot  them.
No  tool,  no  wear  cloth  for  ground.
And  no  one  just  played  the  video
because  of  community  guidelines.
Now,  in  that  video,
he  face  no  show.
The  guy  face  no  show,  but
if  you  hear  the  voice,  the
voice  actually  did  similar.
Right?
So  this  guy  don't  commit
one  or  two  things  since.
When  I  don't  link  him  to  insurgency,
eh,  eh,  eh,  eh,  eh,  eh,  kidnapping
and  all  but  I  don't  go  carry  on.
He  start  to  call  names
now  and  they  go  carry  on.
That's  number  one.
Number  two,  obviously  I'll  give
him  a  peace  deal  as  well.
Because  even  I  think  if  that
guy  forecasting  a  peace  deal,
there's  nothing  people  cannot
do  again  in  this  country.
You  are  giving  a  man  that  has  been
linked  to  quite  a  lot  of  civilians
in  Nigeria,  a  lot  of  citizens.
Nigeria.
Both  women  and  children.
That's  where  they
link  to  kidnappings.
That's  where  we  say  in  all
of  these,  a  lot  of  lives  of
our  own  Nigerian  army,  our
own  military  men  go  down.
They  give  her  a  big  steal
and  they  watch  the  video.
I  just  they  shake  my  head.
That's  why  you  pack  cartridge
pack  bullets  full  body  They
talk  and  they  watch  them.
I  just  they  shake  and  they  laugh.
I  say  no  if  you  look  at  it
critically  you  will  understand
That  when  they  tell  you  that
there's  insurgency  in  nigeria.
Yes  We  have  to  quote  it  like  that
one  wants  to  make  our  video  Do  you
understand  or  want  to  talk  against
it  or  want  to  talk  about  it?
But  do  these  things  really  exist?
Do  you  understand?
They  say,  oh,  they  go
arrest  one  kidnapper.
They  go  arrest  one,
eh,  Boko  Haram  member.
Who  brought  them  in  before?
Who  bring  Boko  Haram  before?
Who  bring  them  in?
The  only  time  where  all  these
politicians  want  me  to  pipe  by
those  boys,  now  when  those  boys
don't  rebel  against  them,  when
the  boys  don't  get  carried  away,
the  tools  where  they  bring,
where  they  will  take  use  of
them  to  do  politics  for  them.
The  boys  don't  start  to  use
them  for  their  own  thing.
At  that  time,  the  government
didn't  do  anything.
But  anyways,  we  are  not
going  to  talk  about  that.
My  own  bise,  the  question  is  this.
She  will  not  arrest  General
Diyahu  because  he  don't
commit  a  lot  of  atrocities.
We  are  going  to  link  his  name  too.
Or  because  he  don't  start
to  call  names  when  he
is  not  supposed  to  call.
You  know,  that's  just
my  harmless  question.
Or  is  it  that  he  is
lying  against  the  governor?
is  it  possible  that  the  governor
did  not  have  any  meeting  with  him
or  he's  just  lying  or  he's  just
saying  it  like  i  want  to  know  i'm
really  curious  what  meeting  is  he
talking  about  what  was  discussed
in  this  meeting  you  know  it  is
to  ask  bro  this  country  anyways