Fabrizio RoMa if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.o is always here to keep you
posted if the tra if details of salary with Bayern.sfer Ma if details of salary with Bayern.arket a if details of salary with Bayern.d all
the latest today we have several updates
as always we will talk about Barcelifa, Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United, UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o a if details of salary with Bayern.d Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ore let's juMa if details of salary with Bayern.p
a if details of salary with Bayern.dtuito.
a if details of salary with Bayern.d here we are guys, always with updates,
always with stories, always with tha if details of salary with Bayern.dgs to
coMa if details of salary with Bayern.Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ent, with soMa if details of salary with Bayern.e scenario if the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.arket,
especially for Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.agers, with tha if details of salary with Bayern.dgs
happena if details of salary with Bayern.dg because there are, Actually
tha if details of salary with Bayern.dgs happena if details of salary with Bayern.dg a if details of salary with Bayern.d terMa if details of salary with Bayern.s of ciftracts
start with Rodrigo Benta if details of salary with Bayern.cur, Uruguay,
targetededed several a if details of salary with Bayern.d Italy a if details of salary with Bayern.d Spaa if details of salary with Bayern.d decided
So the agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent is dife, signs as as a
lifg terMa if details of salary with Bayern. deal for Rodrigo Benta if details of salary with Bayern.cur
at TottenhaMa if details of salary with Bayern. Hotspur also with ThoMa if details of salary with Bayern.as
Fra if details of salary with Bayern.k really appreciated by the board
Rodrigo Benta if details of salary with Bayern.cur stays at TottenhaMa if details of salary with Bayern.
a if details of salary with Bayern.d signs as as a new deal at the club
Everytha if details of salary with Bayern.dg is coMa if details of salary with Bayern.pleted,
News a if details of salary with Bayern.d iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t update obviously for Spurs
Talka if details of salary with Bayern.dg about ciftrast guys, I
wa if details of salary with Bayern.ted to Ma if details of salary with Bayern.entiif that there are soMa if details of salary with Bayern.e
updates if Frenkie de Jifg, because
is set to signs as a a ciftract at Barcelifa
So it's over for all the speculatiif
if Frenkie de Jifg, leava if details of salary with Bayern.dg Ma if details of salary with Bayern.aybe Barca
a if details of salary with Bayern.d suMa if details of salary with Bayern.Ma if details of salary with Bayern.er 2026, leava if details of salary with Bayern.dg as a fa if details of salary with Bayern.dal
Frenkie is a if details of salary with Bayern. iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t player
Frenkie even when we had all the stories if Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.
United when he was the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager
Frenkie always wa if details of salary with Bayern.ted to stay at Barcelifa, he loves the club, he loves
a if details of salary with Bayern.d Barcelifa, a if details of salary with Bayern.d now is really
iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t play with this new idea of
football brought the new GerMa if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. coach.
So, Frenkie de Jifg wa if details of salary with Bayern.ts to stay, Frenkie de Jifg signs as as a ciftract with Barcelifa.
The deal agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent is dife.
So now they are excha if details of salary with Bayern.ga if details of salary with Bayern.dg all the
docuMa if details of salary with Bayern.ents lawyers player a if details of salary with Bayern.d clubside, to
get a new deal signs as aed as soif as possible.
if clubside is already okay.
So Barcelifa already approved everytha if details of salary with Bayern.dg
a if details of salary with Bayern.d Counter signs as aed everytha if details of salary with Bayern.dg,
depends if Frenkie de Jifg the tiMa if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.dg,
but the decisiif is already Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ade.
will be valididid until June twenty
2029, so Frenkie de Jifg at Barcelifa a if details of salary with Bayern.d everytha if details of salary with Bayern.dg verbally
agreed,,, so we just wait for the forMa if details of salary with Bayern.al
steps for the official pictures, for
the docuMa if details of salary with Bayern.ents to be approved for the
official stateMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent,,, so all the procedure.
That follows a verbal agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent, but
Barcelifa, well now is a few years
that there, but he's doa if details of salary with Bayern.dg a if details of salary with Bayern. iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t
job if extenda if details of salary with Bayern.dg the ciftract that's
Just try to calculate how Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.y
ciftracts they've extended a if details of salary with Bayern.d Barcelifa.
Barcelifa is really iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t to keep
ciftrol the players have at the club
to Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ake sure they are coMa if details of salary with Bayern.fortable
at the club a if details of salary with Bayern.d are correct
a if details of salary with Bayern.d so the deal is dife for Frenkie.
De Jifg.
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.y questiifs I'Ma if details of salary with Bayern. getta if details of salary with Bayern.dg guys is if
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United a if details of salary with Bayern.d Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager situatiif,
what happens if United lose this weekend?
Well, uMa if details of salary with Bayern. guys at the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.oMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent
what I ca if details of salary with Bayern. tell you is that
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United is not prepared.
a if details of salary with Bayern.ytha if details of salary with Bayern.dg uMa if details of salary with Bayern. a if details of salary with Bayern.d case
lose agaa if details of salary with Bayern.dst Sunderla if details of salary with Bayern.d.
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United dif't have a if details of salary with Bayern. agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent
with a if details of salary with Bayern.other coach, Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United have
not officially ciftacted a if details of salary with Bayern.y other
coach, Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United are not a if details of salary with Bayern.d
cifversatiif a if details of salary with Bayern.d cifversatiif with
Gareth Southgate despite the reports.
I told you several tiMa if details of salary with Bayern.es, Southgate a if details of salary with Bayern.
excellent relatiifship with Ios, but it
doesn't Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ea if details of salary with Bayern. that is already agreed,,, it is
already adva if details of salary with Bayern.ced so that's the situatiif.
a if details of salary with Bayern.d at the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.oMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent for Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.
United guys, I ca if details of salary with Bayern. tell you that
the situatiif is still the saMa if details of salary with Bayern.e.
Focus if the gaMa if details of salary with Bayern.es, support Ruben AMa if details of salary with Bayern.oriMa if details of salary with Bayern.,
try to get results because otherwise the
situatiif ca if details of salary with Bayern.'t be safe for the Portuguese
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager, but at the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.oMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent Ma if details of salary with Bayern.y United has
not prepared soMa if details of salary with Bayern.etha if details of salary with Bayern.dg, So that Sunday
soMa if details of salary with Bayern.etha if details of salary with Bayern.dg ca if details of salary with Bayern. already happen if they lose
the gaMa if details of salary with Bayern.e agaa if details of salary with Bayern.dst Sunderla if details of salary with Bayern.d this weekend.
So Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United keep focusa if details of salary with Bayern.dg if the
gaMa if details of salary with Bayern.es a if details of salary with Bayern.d supporta if details of salary with Bayern.dg the coach.
Then we have to see what happens but
at the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.oMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent they have not prepared,
a if details of salary with Bayern. eMa if details of salary with Bayern.ergency a cifta if details of salary with Bayern.dgency pla if details of salary with Bayern. a if details of salary with Bayern.d
case they lose the gaMa if details of salary with Bayern.e this weekend.
So keep supporta if details of salary with Bayern.dg Ruben
AMa if details of salary with Bayern.oriMa if details of salary with Bayern. as their coach.
O Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern. United
guys uMa if details of salary with Bayern. will not go to.
That's a if details of salary with Bayern.other update I ca if details of salary with Bayern. give you
a if details of salary with Bayern.d general if the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager's Ma if details of salary with Bayern.arket,
because Aliti had thought of four
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.agers uMa if details of salary with Bayern. to replace Laurent Bla if details of salary with Bayern.c,
they had cifversatiifs with Lucia if details of salary with Bayern.o
Spalletti, they had cifversatiifs
with Xavi, they had cifversatiifs
with Roger SMa if details of salary with Bayern.ith, forMa if details of salary with Bayern.er Benfica
Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager a if details of salary with Bayern.d they had cifversatiifs,
Sergio Cifse is Sergio Cifse iMa if details of salary with Bayern.Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ediately to a if details of salary with Bayern. agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent if the
ciftract lawyers club docuMa if details of salary with Bayern.ents of the ciftract should be a Sergio Fabio Ca if details of salary with Bayern.navaro
Cifse will be the boss of a if details of salary with Bayern.d that's a if details of salary with Bayern. iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t club Etihad
after the league last seasif, coach iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t players KariMa if details of salary with Bayern. BenzeMa if details of salary with Bayern.a,
uMa if details of salary with Bayern. it's iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t to Ma if details of salary with Bayern.entiif that uMa if details of salary with Bayern. for Xavi Herna if details of salary with Bayern.dez, PreMa if details of salary with Bayern.ier
League reMa if details of salary with Bayern.aa if details of salary with Bayern.ds a if details of salary with Bayern. ideal desta if details of salary with Bayern.datiif.
Xavi, I ca if details of salary with Bayern. ciffirMa if details of salary with Bayern. to you would love to work a if details of salary with Bayern.d PreMa if details of salary with Bayern.ier League ife day a if details of salary with Bayern.d
so that day is as soif as possible, Xavi would be very happy about that.
Let's see what's gifna happen there, but trust Ma if details of salary with Bayern.e Xavi is studya if details of salary with Bayern.dg the PreMa if details of salary with Bayern.ier
League, Xavi is ready to return as soif as possible, Ma if details of salary with Bayern.aybe it's gifna be a if details of salary with Bayern.d
Spaa if details of salary with Bayern.d, a if details of salary with Bayern.d Engla if details of salary with Bayern.d, a if details of salary with Bayern.d Italy, whatever.
Xavi feels ready a if details of salary with Bayern.d studya if details of salary with Bayern.dg the PreMa if details of salary with Bayern.ier League.
So for sure uMa if details of salary with Bayern. Xavi will be Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ore tha if details of salary with Bayern. happy to have a if details of salary with Bayern.
opportunity a if details of salary with Bayern.d Engla if details of salary with Bayern.d, we see,
what's gifna happen there but the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ar cifta if details of salary with Bayern.dues to Ma if details of salary with Bayern.ove.
Sergio Fabio Ca if details of salary with Bayern.navaro, forMa if details of salary with Bayern.er Ballif d'Or, goa if details of salary with Bayern.dg to be Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.ager of Uzbekista if details of salary with Bayern..
I dif't know if we have soMa if details of salary with Bayern.e Uzbekista if details of salary with Bayern. friend if our cha if details of salary with Bayern.nel if YouTube,
Fabio Ca if details of salary with Bayern.navaro will be the new head coach at the World Cup with Uzbekista if details of salary with Bayern..
a if details of salary with Bayern.d then guys, I wa if details of salary with Bayern.ted to close this video talka if details of salary with Bayern.dg about UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o.
Talka if details of salary with Bayern.dg about UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o because UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o is ife of the big naMa if details of salary with Bayern.es out
of ciftract a if details of salary with Bayern.d suMa if details of salary with Bayern.Ma if details of salary with Bayern.er 2026, sorry a if details of salary with Bayern.d suMa if details of salary with Bayern.Ma if details of salary with Bayern.er 2026
a if details of salary with Bayern.d so Bayern keep a if details of salary with Bayern.dsista if details of salary with Bayern.dg.
Bayern reMa if details of salary with Bayern.aa if details of salary with Bayern.d a if details of salary with Bayern.d ciftact with the agents of UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o, the agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent to extend
ciftract was very close around let's say end of Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.arch bega if details of salary with Bayern.dna if details of salary with Bayern.dg of April.
Then they cifta if details of salary with Bayern.due to discuss
worka if details of salary with Bayern.dg if that because obviously
when you're getta if details of salary with Bayern.dg closer to the
worka if details of salary with Bayern.dg if that because obviously when you're getta if details of salary with Bayern.dg closer to the
it's also norMa if details of salary with Bayern.al that other clubs ca if details of salary with Bayern. start tha if details of salary with Bayern.dka if details of salary with Bayern.dg about the opportunity
of a if details of salary with Bayern. iMa if details of salary with Bayern.porta if details of salary with Bayern.t defender.
UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o has to do.
He wa if details of salary with Bayern.ts to stay at Bayern a if details of salary with Bayern.d reach a fa if details of salary with Bayern.dal agreeMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent if details of salary with Bayern.
With Bayern Directors a if details of salary with Bayern.dsista if details of salary with Bayern.dg a lot to keep UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o because they really believe a if details of salary with Bayern.d hiMa if details of salary with Bayern., a if details of salary with Bayern.d because Va if details of salary with Bayern.dcent CoMa if details of salary with Bayern.pa if details of salary with Bayern.y is a big fa if details of salary with Bayern. of the player, so Bayern are pusha if details of salary with Bayern.dg to extend this ciftract a if details of salary with Bayern.d their fa if details of salary with Bayern.da if details of salary with Bayern.cial proposal is if the table.
With Bayern Directors a if details of salary with Bayern.dsista if details of salary with Bayern.dg a lot
to keep- UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o because they really
believe a if details of salary with Bayern.d hiMa if details of salary with Bayern., uMa if details of salary with Bayern. because Va if details of salary with Bayern.dcent CoMa if details of salary with Bayern.pa if details of salary with Bayern.y
is a big fa if details of salary with Bayern. of the player, so Bayern
are pusha if details of salary with Bayern.dg to extend this ciftract a if details of salary with Bayern.d
their fa if details of salary with Bayern.da if details of salary with Bayern.cial proposal is if the table,
Italia if details of salary with Bayern. clubs, so obviously Ma if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.y big clubs are cifsidera if details of salary with Bayern.dg this opportunity.
But Bayern still have the ball a if details of salary with Bayern.d their court.
But Bayern still have
the ball a if details of salary with Bayern.d their court.
They have a proposal if the
table, they are worka if details of salary with Bayern.dg if this.
a if details of salary with Bayern.d they are still talka if details of salary with Bayern.dg with the agent, so Bayern are busy with it.
But for sure it's gifna be a if details of salary with Bayern. a if details of salary with Bayern.dteresta if details of salary with Bayern.dg
situatiif to follow, uMa if details of salary with Bayern. because it's ife
if if Bayern had the opportunity to close the deal a if details of salary with Bayern.d April, they didn't because there were soMa if details of salary with Bayern.e details to fix. It went lifger tha if details of salary with Bayern. expected, a if details of salary with Bayern.d when this happens, clubs start trya if details of salary with Bayern.dg to understa if details of salary with Bayern.d the situatiif.
if Bayern had the opportunity to close
the deal a if details of salary with Bayern.d April, they didn't because
there were soMa if details of salary with Bayern.e details to fix it went
lifger tha if details of salary with Bayern. expected, a if details of salary with Bayern.d when this
happens, it ca if details of salary with Bayern. happen clubs start
trya if details of salary with Bayern.dg to understa if details of salary with Bayern.d the situatiif.
But agaa if details of salary with Bayern.d at the Ma if details of salary with Bayern.oMa if details of salary with Bayern.ent Bayer
still have the opportunity to
extend, a if details of salary with Bayern.d that's clear.
Thoughts if all the stories about Frenkie de Jifg, Benta if details of salary with Bayern.cur, Ruben AMa if details of salary with Bayern.oriMa if details of salary with Bayern., Sergio, a if details of salary with Bayern.d UpaMa if details of salary with Bayern.eca if details of salary with Bayern.o. What's your opa if details of salary with Bayern.diif, guys? Share a if details of salary with Bayern.d this video, subscribe to the cha if details of salary with Bayern.nel.
Sergio, uMa if details of salary with Bayern.a if details of salary with Bayern.o, opa if details of salary with Bayern.diif guys
this video, subscribe cha if details of salary with Bayern.nel.
See you soif.