Fabrizio Romano is always here to keep you
posted on the transfer market and all
the latest today we have several updates
Barcelona, Man United, Upamecano and more let's jump.
Intuito.
And here we are guys, always with updates,
always with stories, always with things to
comment, with some scenario on the market,
especially for managers, with things
happening because there are, Actually
things happening in terms of contracts
and still big on the market, let me
start with Rodrigo Bentancur, Uruguay,
targeted several in Italy and Spain decided
So the agreement is done is signed a
long term deal for Rodrigo Bentancur
who is staying at Tottenham is gonna be,
Part of the project, long term project
at Tottenham Hotspur also with Thomas
Frank really appreciated by the board
and all the people at the club and so,
Rodrigo Bentancur stays at Tottenham
and science a New Deal at the club.
Everything is completed
and it's an important.
News and important update
obviously for Spurs.
Talking about contrast guys, I
wanted to mention that there are some
updates on Frenkie de Jong, because
is set to sign contract at Barcelona.
leaving maybe Barca in summer twenty twenty-six, leaving as, um Every agent maybe after, so
in summer twenty twenty six, leaving
as, um Every agent maybe after, so
many stories on Frenkie de Jong always, but he is an important player.
Frenkie de Jong even when we had all the stories on Man United when he was the manager.
United when was the manager.
Frenkie always wanted to stay at
Barcelona, he loves the club, he loves
in Barcelona, and now is really
important to play with this new idea of
So, Frenkie de Jong wants to stay, Frenkie de Jong signs a contract in Barcelona.
The deal agreement is done.
So now they are exchanging all the
documents lawyers player and clubside, to
get a new deal signed as soon as possible.
On clubside is already okay.
So Barcelona already approved everything
and Counter signed everything,
depends on Frenkie de Jong the timing,
but the decision is already made.
will be valid until June twenty
twenty-nine, so Frenkie de Jong at Barcelona and everything verbally
agreed, so we just wait for the formal
the documents to be approved for the official statement, so all the procedure.
That follows a verbal agreement, but
Frenkie de Jong will be part of Barcelona
news for Barça, and especially a part
of the Deco project. I always mention
Barcelona, well now is a few years
that there, but he's doing an important
job on extending the contract, that's
um Just try to calculate how many
contracts they've extended in Barcelona.
Barcelona is really important to keep
control the players have at the club
to make sure they are comfortable
at the club and are correct
and so the deal is done for Frenkie de Jong.
De Jong.
My questions I'm getting guys is on
Man United and manager situation,
what happens if United lose this weekend?
Well, um guys at the moment
what I can tell you is that
Man United is not prepared.
Anything um in case
lose against Sunderland.
Man United don't have an agreement
with another coach, Man United have
not officially contacted any other
coach, Man United are not in
conversation in conversation with
Gareth Southgate despite the reports.
I told you several times, Southgate an
excellent relationship with Ios, but it
doesn't mean that is already agreed, it is
already advanced so that's the situation.
And at the moment for Manchester
United guys, I can tell you that
the situation is still the same.
Focus on the games, support Ruben Amorim,
try to get results because otherwise the
situation can't be safe for the Portuguese
manager, but at the moment my United has
not prepared something, So that Sunday
something can already happen if they lose
the game against Sunderland this weekend.
So Man United keep focusing on the
games and supporting the coach.
Then we have to see what happens but
at the moment they have not prepared,
an emergency a contingency plan in
case they lose the game this weekend.
So keep supporting Ruben
Amorim as their coach.
O Man United
guys um will not go to.
That's another update I can give you
in general on the manager's market,
because Aliti had thought of four
managers um to replace Laurent Blanc,
they had conversations with Luciano
Spalletti, they had conversations
with Xavi, they had conversations
with Roger Smith, former Benfica
Xavi
Sergio Conse race is Sergio Conse
immediately to an agreement on the
Sergio Fabio Cannavaro
Conse will be the boss of and that's
an important important club Etihad
after the league last season, coach
important players Karim Benzema,
um it's important to mention That
um for Xavi Hernandez, Premier
League remains an ideal destination.
Xavi, I can confront to you would love
to work in Premier League one day and
so that day is as soon as possible,
Xavi would be very happy about that.
Let's see what's gonna happen there, but
trust me Xavi is studying the Premier
League, Xavi is ready to return as
soon as possible, maybe it's gonna be in
Spain, in England, in Italy, whatever.
Xavis feels ready and
studying the Premier League.
So for sure um Xavi will be
more than happy to have an
opportunity in England, we see,
what's gonna happen there but the
manager mar continues to move.
Upamecano
I don't know if we have some Uzbekistan
friend on our channel on YouTube,
Fabio Cannavaro will be the new head
coach at the World Cup with Uzbekistan.
Upamecano
um and so Bayern keep insisting.
contract was very close around let's
say end of March beginning of April.
discussions
working on that because obviously
when you're getting closer to the
the actual contract
it's also normal that other clubs, can
start thinking about the opportunity
defender
Upamecano
He wants to stay at Bayern and reach a final agreement on details of salary with Bayern.
details of salary with Bayern.
With Bayern Directors insisting a lot
to keep- Upamecano because they really
believe in him, um because Vincent Company
is a big fan of the player, so Bayern
are pushing to extend this contract and
their financial proposal is on the table,
English, Spanish, Italian clubs
Italian clubs, so obviously many big
clubs are considering this opportunity.
But Bayern still have
the ball in their court.
They have a proposal on the
table, they are working on this.
agent
But for sure it's gonna be an interesting
situation to follow, um because it's one
in 2026
if Bayern had the opportunity
there were some details to fix it went
longer than expected, and when this
happens, it can happen clubs start
trying to understand the situation.
But again at the moment Bayer
still have the opportunity to
that's clear
Thoughts on all the stories about Frenkie de Jong, Bentancur, Ruben Amorim, Sergio, Upamecano. What's your opinion, guys? Share in the comments, subscribe to the channel.
Sergio, umano, opinion guys
this video, subscribe channel.
See you soon.