Hey guys, welcome back to the channel Fabrizio Romano is always to keep you
posted on the transfer market and all the latest today we have several updates
as always we will talk about, Barcelona, Man United, Upamecano e more let's jump.
And here we are guys, always with updates, always with stories, always with things to
comment, with some scenario on the market, especially for managers, with things
happening because there are, things happening in terms of contracts
and still big on the market, let me start with Rodrigo Bentancourt, Uruguai,
target several in Italy in Spain decided to sign contract at Tottenham Hotspur.
the agreement is done is signed a long term deal for Rodrigo Bentancourt
who is staying at Tottenham is gonna be, Part of the project, long term project
at Tottenham Hotspur also with Thomas Frank really appreciated by the board
and all the people at the club and Rodrigo Bentancourt stays at Tottenham
and science a New Deal at the club.
Everything is completed and it's an important.
News and important update obviously for Spurs.
Talking about contract guys, I wanted to mention that there are some
updates on Frankie de Jong, because as reported by sport, Frankie de Jong
is set to sign contract at Barcelona.
it's over for all the speculation on Frankie de Jong, leaving maybe Barca
in summer twenty twenty six, leaving as, Every agent maybe after,
many stories on Frankie de Jong always, but weak is an important player.
Frankie de Jong even when we had all the stories on Manchester
United when was the manager.
Frankie always wanted to stay at Barcelona, he loves the club, he loves
the city, he feels very comfortable in Barcelona, and now is really
important play with this new idea of football brought the new German coach.
Frankie de Jong wants to stay, Frankie de Jong sign contract in Barcelona.
the ball agreement is done.
now they are exchanging all the documents lawyers player and clubside, to
get a new deal signed as soon as possible.
On clubside is already
Barcelona already approved everything and Counter signed everything,
depends on Frankie de Jong the timing, but the decision is already made.
Frankie sign contra Barcelona will be val until June twenty
twenty-nine, Frankie de Jong at Barcelona and everything verbally
agreed we just wait for the formal steps for the official pictures, for
the documents to be approved for the official statement all the procedure.
That follows a verbal agreement, but Frankie de Jong will be part of Barcelona
project and I think he's an excellent news for Barca, and especially part
of the Deco project, I always mention to you this, but the new Director of
Barcelona, now is a few years that there, but he's doing an important
job on extending the contract, that's really really really important for Deco.
Just try to calculate how many contacts the extended in Barcelona.
In in the recent, maybe in the last twelve months, maybe or contracts.
Barcelona is really important to keep control the players have at the club
to make sure they are comfortable
at the club andar correct for Barcelona financial play
and deal done for Frankie.
The Young.
My questions I'm getting guys is on Manchester United and manager situation,
what happens if United lose this weekend?
guys at the moment what I can tell you is that
Manchester United is not prepared.
Anything in case lose against Sunderland.
Man United don't have an agreement with another coach, Man United have
not officially contacted any other coach, Manchester United are not in
conversation in conversation with Gareth Southgate despite the reports.
I told you several times, Southgate an excellent relationship with Ios, but it
doesn't mean that is already agreed, it is already advanced that's the situation.
And at the moment for Manchester United guys, I can tell you that
the situation is still the same.
Focus on the games, support Ruben Amorim, try to get results because otherwise the
situation can't be safe for the Portuguese manager, but at the moment my United has
not prepared something, that Sunday something can already happen if they lose
the game against Sunderland this weekend.
M United keep focusing on the games and supporting the coach.
Than we have to see what happens but at the moment they have not prepared,
an emergency a contingency plan in case they lose the game this weekend.
keep supporting Ruben Amorim as their coach.
O Manchester United guys will not go to.
That's another update I can give you in general on the manager's market,
because Aliti had thought of four managers to replace Laurent Blanc,
they had conversations with Luciano Spalletti, they had conversations
with Xvi, they had conversations with Roger Smith, former Benfica
manager and they had conversations,
Sergio Conse race is Sergio Conse immediately to an agreement on the
contract lawyers club documents of the contract should be a Sergio Conse
Conse will be the boss of and that's an important important club Etihad
after the league last season, coach important players Karim Benzema,
it's important to mention That for Xavi Hernandez, Premier
League remains an ideal destination.
Xavi, I can confront to you would love to work in Premier League one day and
that day is as soon as possible, Xavi would be very happy about that.
Let's see what's gonna happen there, but trust me Chavi is studying the Premier
League, Chavi is ready to return as soon as possible, maybe it's gonna be in
Spain, in England, in Italy, whatever.
Chavis feels ready and studying the Premier League.
for sure Chavi will be more then happy to have an
opportunity in England, we see,
what's gonna happen there but the manager mar continues to move.
Sergio Fabio Cannavaro, former Ballon d'or, going to be manager of Uzbekistan.
I don't know if we have some Uzbekistan friend on our channel on YouTube,
Fabio Cannavaro will be the new head coach at the World Cup with Uzbekistan.
And than guys, I wanted to close this video talking about Upamano.
Talking about Upamekano because Upamekano is one of the big names out
of contact in summer twenty twenty-five, sorry in summer twenty twenty-six
and Bayern keep insisting.
Bayern remain in contact with the agents of UpaUpamecano, the agreement to extend
contract was very close around let's say end of March beginning of April.
Than they continue to discussos and at the moment they are still
working on that because obviously when you're getting closer to the
the the the the the actual contract,
it's also normal that other clubs, can start thinking about the opportunity
of an important defenderano.
Superano has to do.
he wants to stay at Bayern and reach an agreement final
details of salary with Bayern.
With Bayern Directors insisting a lot to keep- UpaUpamecano because they really
believe in him, because Vincent Company is a big fan of the player, Bayern
are pushing to extend this contract and their financial proposal is on the table,
O U Mano wants to listen clubs, there is interest from English, Spanish,
Italian clubs, obviously many big clubs are considering this opportunity.
But Bayern still have the ball in their court.
They have a proposal on the table, they are working on this.
And they are still talking with the agano, Bayern are busy with it.
But for sure it's gonna be an interesting situation to follow, because it's one
of the big names potentially available on a free in twenty twenty-six, depends
on Bayern had the opportunity to close the deal in April, they didn't because
there were some details to fix it went longer then expected, and when this
happens, it can happen clubs start trying to understand the situation.
But again at the moment Bayer still have the opportunity to
extend and that's they clear.
guys thoughts on all the stories Frankie de Jong, Tancur, Ruben Amorim,
Sergio, umano, opinion guys this video, subscribe channel.
See you soon.