Hey guys, welcome back to the channel
Fabrizio Romano is always to keep you
posted on the transfer market and all
the latest today we have several updates
as always we will talk about, Barcelona,
May United, Mecano e more let's jump.
Intuito.
And here we are guys, always with updates,
always with stories, always with things to
comment, with some scenario on the market,
especially for managers, with things
happening because there are, Actually
things happening in terms of contracts
and still big on the market, let me
start with Rodrigo Bentancourt, Uruguai,
target several in Italy in Spain decided
to sign contract at Tottenham Hotspur.
So the agreement is done is signed a
long term deal for Rodrigo Bentancourt
who is staying at Tottenham is gonna be,
Part of the project, long term project
at Tottenham Hotspur also with Thomas
Frank really appreciated by the board
and all the people at the club and so,
Rodrigo Bentancourt stays at Tottenham
and science a New Deal at the club.
Everything is completed
and it's an important.
News and important update
obviously for Spurs.
Talking about contrast guys, I
wanted to mention that there are some
updates on Frankie de Jong, because
as reported by sport, Frankie de Jong
is set to sign contract at Barcelona.
So it's over for all the speculation
on Frankie de Jong, leaving maybe Barca
in summer twenty twenty six, leaving
as, um Every agent maybe after, so
many stories on Frankie de Jong always,
but weak is an important player.
Frankie de Jong even when we had
all the stories on Manchester
United when was the manager.
Frankie always wanted to stay at
Barcelona, he loves the club, he loves
the city, he feels very comfortable
in Barcelona, and now is really
important play with this new idea of
football brought the new German coach.
So, Frankie de Jong wants to stay, Frankie
de Jong sign contract in Barcelona.
Thebal agreement is done.
So now they are exchanging all the
documents lawyers player and clubside, to
get a new deal signed as soon as possible.
On clubside is already okay.
So Barcelona already approved everything
and Counter signed everything,
depends on Frankie de Jong the timing,
but the decision is already made.
Frankie sign contra Barcelona
will be val until June twenty
twenty-nine, so Frankie de Jong at
Barcelona and everything verbally
agreed so we just wait for the formal
steps for the official pictures, for
the documents to be approved for the
official statement so all the procedure.
That follows a verbal agreement, but
Frankie de Jong will be part of Barcelona
project and I think he's an excellent
news for Barca, and especially part
of the Deco project, I always mention
to you this, but the new Director of
Barcelona, well now is a few years
that there, but he's doing an important
job on extending the contract, that's
really really really important for Deco.
um Just try to calculate how many
contacts the extended in Barcelona.
In in the recent, um maybe in the last
twelve months, maybe like or contracts.
Barcelona is really important to keep
control the players have at the club
to make sure they are comfortable
at the club andar correct
for Barcelona financial play
and so deal done for Frankie.
The Young.
My questions I'm getting guys is on
Manchester United and manager situation,
what happens if United lose this weekend?
Well, um guys at the moment
what I can tell you is that
Manchester United is not prepared.
Anything um in case
lose against Sunderland.
May United don't have an agreement
with another coach, May United have
not officially contacted any other
coach, Manchester United are not in
conversation in conversation with
Gareth Southgate despite the reports.
I told you several times, Southgate an
excellent relationship with Ios, but it
doesn't mean that is already agreed, it is
already advanced so that's the situation.
And at the moment for Manchester
United guys, I can tell you that
the situation is still the same.
Focus on the games, support Ruben Amorim,
try to get results because otherwise the
situation can't be safe for the Portuguese
manager, but at the moment my United has
not prepared something, So that Sunday
something can already happen if they lose
the game against Sunderland this weekend.
So M United keep focusing on the
games and supporting the coach.
Then we have to see what happens but
at the moment they have not prepared,
an emergency a contingency plan in
case they lose the game this weekend.
So keep supporting Ruben
Amorim as their coach.
O Manchester United
guys um will not go to.
That's another update I can give you
in general on the manager's market,
because Aliti had thought of four
managers um to replace Laurent Blanc,
they had conversations with Luciano
Spalletti, they had conversations
with Xvi, they had conversations
with Roger Smith, former Benfica
manager and they had conversations,
Sergio Conse race is Sergio Conse
immediately to an agreement on the
contract lawyers club documents of the
contract should be a Sergio Conse so
Conse will be the boss of and that's
an important important club Etihad
after the league last season, coach
important players Karim Benzema,
um it's important to mention That
um for Xavi Hernandez, Premier
League remains an ideal destination.
Xavi, I can confront to you would love
to work in Premier League one day and
so that day is as soon as possible,
Xavi would be very happy about that.
Let's see what's gonna happen there, but
trust me Chavi is studying the Premier
League, Chavi is ready to return as
soon as possible, maybe it's gonna be in
Spain, in England, in Italy, whatever.
Chavis feels ready and
studying the Premier League.
So for sure um Chavi will be
more than happy to have an
opportunity in England, we see,
what's gonna happen there but the
manager mar continues to move.
Sergio Fabio Cannavaro, former Ballon
d'or, going to be manager of Uzbekistan.
I don't know if we have some Uzbekistan
friend on our channel on YouTube,
Fabio Cannavaro will be the new head
coach at the World Cup with Uzbekistan.
And then guys, I wanted to close
this video talking about Upamano.
Talking about Upamekano because
Upamekano is one of the big names out
of contact in summer twenty twenty-five,
sorry in summer twenty twenty-six
um and so Bayern keep insisting.
Bayern remain in contact with the agents
of Upamecano, um the agreement to extend
contract was very close around let's
say end of March beginning of April.
Then they continue to discussos
and at the moment they are still
working on that because obviously
when you're getting closer to the
the the the the the actual contract,
it's also normal that other clubs, can
start thinking about the opportunity
of an important defenderano.
Superano has to do.
um he wants to stay at Bayern
and reach an agreement final
details of salary with Bayern.
With Bayern Directors insisting a lot
to keep- Upamecano because they really
believe in him, um because Vincent Company
is a big fan of the player, so Bayern
are pushing to extend this contract and
their financial proposal is on the table,
O U Mano wants to listen clubs, there
is interest from English, Spanish,
Italian clubs, so obviously many big
clubs are considering this opportunity.
But Bayern still have
the ball in their court.
They have a proposal on the
table, they are working on this.
And they are still talking with the
agano, so Bayern are busy with it.
But for sure it's gonna be an interesting
situation to follow, um because it's one
of the big names potentially available
on a free in twenty twenty-six, depends
on Bayern had the opportunity to close
the deal in April, they didn't because
there were some details to fix it went
longer than expected, and when this
happens, it can happen clubs start
trying to understand the situation.
But again at the moment Bayer
still have the opportunity to
extend and that's they clear.
so guys thoughts on all the stories
Frankie de Jong, Tancur, Ruben Amorim,
Sergio, umano, opinion guys
this video, subscribe channel.
See you soon.